Luke Thomson

Technical Artist

contact@floofinator.com - Please ask for Address - Please ask for Phone Number

OBJECTIVE

As a technical artist, I focus on creative production through technical understanding. My goal is to use technology and the functionality it allows to create experiences for others to be entertained. My focus is on the creation of entertainment through computer programming, graphics, and animation.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science in Game Development and Simulation

Florida Polytechnic University - Lakeland, FL. Graduated April 2024

KEY SKILLS

Programming Languages - C++, C#, Java, JavaScript, Python, Lua, GDScript

Graphics Programming - HLSL, GLSL, Visual Shader Graph

Management - Git, GitHub, Team Organization, Design Documentation

3D Modelling, Texturing, Rigging, Animation - Blender, Maya

2D Art and Animation - Clip Studio Paint, Krita, Photoshop

Web Development - HTML, CSS, JavaScript, REST, APIs, Node.js, React.js, Vue.js

EXPERIENCE

ENA - Power of Potluck - 3D Modelling and Animation

Joel G EIRL - Remote. November 2023

- Remote work on the ENA series animated short, Power of Potluck. Episode: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TmXe-ZGr5RM
- 3D Modelling, 3D Animation

ENA - Dream BBQ - Technical Artist

Joel G EIRL - Remote. April 2022 - Present

- Remote work on the ENA series game, Dream BBQ. Yet to be released. Trailer: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qLurAhsqXWc
- 3D Animation, 2D Animation, Game Engine Asset Integration, VFX development

2nd Place Undergraduate FIEA Statewide Game Jam

Florida Interactive Entertainment Academy - Orlando, FL. January 2024

- Developed a game in a team of 4 in under 48 hours.
- Modeled 3D assets while integrating textures from 2D artist. Created 3D Animation and programmed visual effects.
- Communicated goals and necessary tasks with the team to ensure work was formed into a viable product by the deadline.
- https://fiea.ucf.edu/news/fiea-and-florida-polytechnic-students-win-fieas-first-game-jam/

FSI NASA DON- Distributed Observer Network

Florida Space Institute - Orlando, FL. April 2023 - April 2024

- Ported previous Unity program to Unreal Engine.
- Researched and applied engine tools to represent an optimized heightmap of the moon's south pole.
- Communicated with previous teams and sponsor to establish tasks and goals before the end of the capstone period.
- Presented project description and progress through many presentations throughout the 2 semesters to a team of evaluators.

Club Vice President

Florida Poly Media Club - Lakeland, FL. 2021 – 2022

- Managed club budget and purchase requests for events.
- Organized Florida Poly Respawn Game Jam and Game Expo.

Personal Projects

2019 – On Going

- Created multiple game prototypes around a theme in only 48 hours.
- Planned and organized tasks independently to manage scope and resources.
- Developed and released multiple game projects to Itch.io. https://floofinator.itch.io/
- Created and hosted a personal website. https://floofinator.com/

HOBBIES

Drawing, Piano, Clay, Electronics and other crafts.

references available upon request